<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Crime - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/crime.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Chain Snatching Prevention Tips: Stay Safe in Public</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/be-aware-of-chain-snatchers-tips-to-prevent-chain-snatching.html</link>
			<description>Chain snatching is one of the fastest-growing street crimes across India. It happens suddenly, often within seconds, and leaves the victim shocked, shaken, and sometimes even injured. The criminals involved in chain snatching usually work in pairs or small groups and target vulnerable individuals in public spaces. Unlike bigger crimes like robbery, burglary, or house break-ins, chain snatching is </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:38:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/be-aware-of-chain-snatchers-tips-to-prevent-chain-snatching.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prime accused in gang-rape case nabbed after two decades</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prime-accused-in-gang-rape-case-nabbed-after-two-decades.html</link>
			<description>Prime accused Bibekananda Biswal in a sensational gangrape that shook Odisha in its aftermath in 1999 is now caught by Police from Aamby Valley in Lonavala in Maharashtra.                                The incident, that occurred in 1999, had created a state-wide outrage. A total of three persons were accused in the case. Two of them - Pradeep Sahi and Dhirendra Mohanty, were arrested and convict</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prime-accused-in-gang-rape-case-nabbed-after-two-decades.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Reduce the Risk of Becoming a Sexual Assault Victim!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reduce-the-risk-of-becoming-a-sexual-assault-victim.html</link>
			<description>To Reduce the risk for you to becoming a sexual victim, you have to take some preventative measures, which will help you to avoid a risky situations from escalating. Anyone can be the target of sexual assault, regardless of age, gender, race, ethnicity, sexual orientation, sexual history, or social class. There is no stereotypical victim or rapist.                                What's bad? - Near</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reduce-the-risk-of-becoming-a-sexual-assault-victim.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>