<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Marriage - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/marriage.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>What Is the Best Age to Get Married — And Why? Key Perspectives</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-the-best-age-to-get-married-and-why.html</link>
			<description>&amp;ldquo;What is the best age to get married?&amp;rdquo; This is one of the most frequently searched questions around relationships and life planning. While many people hope for a specific age&amp;mdash;25, 28, 30&amp;mdash;there is no universal best age that guarantees a successful marriage. The ideal age differs from person to person and depends on several factors including emotional maturity, financial stabi</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:47:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-the-best-age-to-get-married-and-why.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What Happened at That Wedding? Real Stories &amp; Emotional Reflections</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-happened-at-a-wedding-that-made-you-feel-horrible-in-india.html</link>
			<description>Weddings are typically joyous occasions, but sometimes, unexpected events can cast a shadow over the celebration, leading to feelings of empathy and sadness for the bride.  Here are a few hypothetical scenarios that could make someone feel horrible for Groom or Bride:  1. Dowry Dispute   A groom or his family demanding additional dowry at the last minute, sometimes even refusing to proceed with th</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-happened-at-a-wedding-that-made-you-feel-horrible-in-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Indian Husband vs Foreign Husband: Key Cultural Differences</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/difference-between-an-indian-husband-and-foreign-husband.html</link>
			<description>The experiences of husbands can vary significantly based on cultural, social and regional contexts. Here are some general differences between Indian husbands and husbands from other cultures (referred to here as &amp;quot;foreign husbands&amp;quot;).  Please note that these differences are not absolute and individual experiences may vary widely within each category:  1. Cultural Norms and Expectations:   </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/difference-between-an-indian-husband-and-foreign-husband.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What’s Life Like for an Indian Housewife? Culture &amp; Daily Reality</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-it-like-being-an-indian-housewife.html</link>
			<description>Being an Indian housewife can be a complex and varied experience, as it can differ significantly based on factors such as family dynamics, cultural background, personal choices and societal changes.  Here are some general aspects that might characterize the experience of being an Indian housewife:   Roles and Responsibilities: Indian housewives often take on a range of roles and responsibilities w</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-it-like-being-an-indian-housewife.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Life as an Indian Husband: Culture, Challenges &amp; Insights</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-it-like-being-an-indian-husband.html</link>
			<description>Being an Indian husband can vary greatly based on individual circumstances, cultural background, family values and personal choices.  Here are some general aspects that might characterize the experience of being an Indian husband:   Family Values: In many Indian cultures, family plays a central role. Being an Indian husband often involves upholding family values, maintaining strong relationships w</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:59:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-it-like-being-an-indian-husband.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Is Life Worth Living Without Marriage? Perspectives &amp; Insights</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-life-worth-living-without-marriage.html</link>
			<description>Is life worth living without marriage? Yes &amp;mdash; absolutely.  Marriage is a choice, not a requirement for a meaningful life. Not everyone wants marriage, and not everyone finds their happiness inside it. A person&amp;rsquo;s value, purpose, and success are not measured by their marital status. What truly matters is how fulfilled, peaceful, and content someone feels in their own journey.  Life can be</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-life-worth-living-without-marriage.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How People Feel When Their Ex Gets Married: Emotional Insights</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-people-feel-when-their-ex-gets-married.html</link>
			<description>When an ex-partner gets married, people can experience a wide range of emotions, depending on their individual circumstances, the nature of their past relationship and their current emotional state.  Here are some common feelings that people might experience:   Surprise: Learning about an ex&amp;#39;s marriage can trigger surprise, especially if there were no indications or prior knowledge of their ne</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-people-feel-when-their-ex-gets-married.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Life of a Divorced Man in India: Challenges &amp; Perspectives</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-is-the-life-of-a-divorced-man-in-india.html</link>
			<description>The life of a divorced man in India can vary greatly depending on several factors, including cultural background, financial stability, social support, personal resilience and geographical location.  Here are some aspects to consider:  Social Stigma and Cultural Perception   Stigma: Although societal attitudes are slowly changing, divorce can still carry a significant stigma in many parts of India.</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-is-the-life-of-a-divorced-man-in-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Indian vs Foreign Housewife: Key Differences Explained</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/difference-between-an-indian-housewife-and-foreign-housewife.html</link>
			<description>The experiences of housewives can vary significantly based on cultural, social and regional contexts. Here are some general differences between Indian housewives and housewives from other cultures (referred to here as &amp;quot;foreign housewives&amp;quot;).  It&amp;#39;s important to note that these differences are not absolute and individual experiences may vary widely within each category:  1. Cultural Con</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/difference-between-an-indian-housewife-and-foreign-housewife.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>South Indian Hindu Marriage: Andhra Style Traditions &amp; Rituals</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/south-indian-hindu-marriage-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>South Indian Hindu weddings, especially in Andhra Pradesh, are known for their rich cultural traditions, meaningful rituals, and the strong involvement of both families. These marriages usually happen over one or more days and include mehndi, haldi, poojas, welcoming ceremonies, and several customs that mark the couple&amp;rsquo;s journey into married life.  While every family may follow traditions sl</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:38:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/south-indian-hindu-marriage-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are the most disturbing truth about marriage?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-most-disturbing-truth-about-marriage.html</link>
			<description>One of the most disturbing truths about marriage is that it doesn't guarantee happiness or permanence. Despite the idealized portrayal of marriage in media and society, the reality is that marriages can face challenges and difficulties.  Here are a few aspects that some may find disturbing:   High Divorce Rates: In many parts of the world, divorce rates are significant, indicating that not all mar</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 18:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-most-disturbing-truth-about-marriage.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>My husband loves me but clearly fancies a woman at work. How can I manage my jealousy?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/my-husband-loves-me-but-clearly-fancies-a-woman-at-work-how-can-i-manage-my-jealousy.html</link>
			<description>Dealing with jealousy in a relationship can be challenging, especially when you feel your partner is attracted to someone else.  Here are some steps you can take to manage your feelings and address the situation constructively:  1. Acknowledge Your Feelings   Why: Recognizing your emotions is the first step in managing them. How: Accept that it’s normal to feel jealous and give yourself permissi</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2024 10:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/my-husband-loves-me-but-clearly-fancies-a-woman-at-work-how-can-i-manage-my-jealousy.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>For what reasons do relationships fail?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-what-reasons-do-relationships-fail.html</link>
			<description>Relationships can fail for various reasons and the dynamics of each relationship are unique.  However, there are some common factors that can contribute to relationship failure:   Poor Communication:   Communication breakdown is one of the primary reasons relationships fail. Lack of effective communication can lead to misunderstandings, unresolved conflicts and feelings of resentment.   Lack of Tr</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-what-reasons-do-relationships-fail.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Signs that your relationship has reached its end</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/signs-that-your-relationship-has-reached-its-end.html</link>
			<description>Deciding when a relationship has reached its end can be a complex and emotionally challenging process. While every relationship is unique, certain signs may indicate that it's time to consider ending a relationship.  Here are some potential signs:   Lack of Communication: Communication is a cornerstone of a healthy relationship. If communication has become strained or there's a constant breakdown </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/signs-that-your-relationship-has-reached-its-end.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How can you spice up your married life?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-you-spice-up-your-married-life.html</link>
			<description>Spicing up your married life can bring renewed excitement, intimacy and connection to your relationship. Here are some suggestions to help you add spice and enhance your married life:   Open Communication: Talk openly and honestly with your partner about your desires, fantasies and what you both want to explore in your relationship. Effective communication is key to understanding each other's need</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 14:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-you-spice-up-your-married-life.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How Introverts can Deal with Marriage</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-introverts-can-deal-with-marriage.html</link>
			<description>Introverts can navigate marriage successfully by understanding and honoring their unique needs and preferences. Here are some tips for introverts on how to deal with marriage:   Communication: Communicate openly with your partner about your introverted nature. Help them understand that you require alone time to recharge and process your thoughts. Discuss your communication styles, boundaries and n</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 11:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-introverts-can-deal-with-marriage.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten Most Common Marriage Questions and Answers</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-most-common-marriage-questions-and-answers.html</link>
			<description>Here are ten common marriage questions along with brief answers:  How can we improve communication in our marriage?   Answer: Prioritize active listening, express yourself honestly and respectfully and seek to understand each other's perspectives.   How do we handle conflicts and disagreements?   Answer: Approach conflicts with empathy, compromise and a willingness to find mutually satisfactory so</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 07:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-most-common-marriage-questions-and-answers.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Lessons to be learnt from Marriage</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-to-be-learnt-from-marriage.html</link>
			<description>Marriage is a complex and deeply personal experience and the lessons one can learn from it can vary based on individual circumstances. However, here are some common lessons that people often learn from their marriages:   Communication is key: Effective communication is crucial for a healthy and thriving marriage. Learning to express your thoughts, emotions and needs openly and honestly, while also</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-to-be-learnt-from-marriage.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Expectations and Freedom in a Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</link>
			<description>People having expectations in a relationship and willing to have freedom in relationships are few of the main reasons for not having a peaceful and healthy relationship with each other.  Having or Setting some unrealistic expectations to have in a relationship can contribute to ending their marriage.  Honestly both the people should be open in communication to each other in terms of the expectatio</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>