<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Ooty - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ooty.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kochi Road Trip (2–3 Days): Itinerary for Solo Riders and Family Travelers</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A road trip from Bangalore to Kochi is one of the most scenic and enriching journeys you can experience in South India. Whether you are riding solo on a motorbike or traveling with your family in a car, this 2&amp;ndash;3 day road trip plan helps you explore multiple destinations&amp;mdash;not just Kochi but also Mysore, Bandipur, Ooty, and Coimbatore&amp;mdash;along the way.  Kochi, known historically as the</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 08:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Ooty 3 Day Trip Plan – Best Itinerary for Couples &amp; Families</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/three-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-ooty.html</link>
			<description>A three-day trip from Bangalore to Ooty is one of the most refreshing getaways you can plan, whether you are a couple riding on a bike or a family driving in a car. Ooty&amp;mdash;often called The Queen of Hill Stations&amp;mdash;offers misty mountains, cool breezes, lush tea gardens, and breathtaking viewpoints that make the journey unforgettable.  If you love long drives, peaceful nature, and a balanced</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 08:37:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/three-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-ooty.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten best hill stations to Travel Solo in South India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo to hill stations in South India offers a unique blend of tranquility, adventure and scenic beauty.  Here are ten of the best hill stations in South India for solo travelers:   Munnar, Kerala   Known for its tea gardens, rolling hills and pleasant weather, Munnar is a great destination for solo travelers. The serene environment and numerous trekking trails make it ideal for exploring</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 08:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best places in South India to travel in Hot Summer?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</link>
			<description>South India offers several destinations that are perfect for traveling during hot summers due to their cooler climates, hill stations and coastal areas.  Here are some of the best places to visit in South India during the hot summer months, along with reasons, ways to travel and the best time to visit:    Ooty, Tamil Nadu:   Why: Ooty, also known as the "Queen of Hill Stations," offers cool temper</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 08:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>