<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Sci-Tech - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sci-tech.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Marshmallow Catapult: A Fun &amp; Easy STEM Experiment for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/marshmallow-catapult-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Science experiments become more exciting when children can build something with their own hands&amp;mdash;and even launch a marshmallow across the room! A marshmallow catapult is a simple but powerful STEM activity that helps kids understand force, motion, energy, and projectile trajectory through play.  In this article, you&amp;rsquo;ll learn how to make a marshmallow catapult at home using basic craft m</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 09:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/marshmallow-catapult-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Magnetic Slime Experiment for Kids: A Fun Way to Learn About Magnetism &amp; Chemistry</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Magnetic slime is one of the most exciting and hands-on science experiments for children. It combines the fun of making slime with the magic of magnetism, allowing kids to explore how magnetic fields work in an enjoyable and interactive way. This simple activity helps children understand chemistry, physics, cause-and-effect, and scientific observation.  Magnetic slime can stretch, move and crawl t</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 09:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Homemade Lava Lamp Experiment for Kids: Learn About Density &amp; Immiscible Liquids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lava-lamp-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Science experiments are one of the best ways to help children learn important concepts while having fun. A homemade lava lamp is a simple, colorful and exciting activity that teaches kids about density, immiscible liquids, and gas reactions using basic materials found at home.  This step-by-step guide explains how to make a lava lamp, the science behind it, safety tips and additional learning idea</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 17:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lava-lamp-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>INS Vikrant Delivered to Indian Navy: Indias First Indigenous Aircraft Carrier</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</link>
			<description>In a historic milestone for India&amp;rsquo;s defense and shipbuilding industry, INS Vikrant, also known as Indigenous Aircraft Carrier 1 (IAC-1), has been delivered to the Indian Navy. This achievement marks India&amp;rsquo;s entry into the exclusive league of countries capable of designing and building aircraft carriers domestically.  INS Vikrant is not just a warship; it is a symbol of technological ex</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:47:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Coffee Ground Fossils: A Fun Science Experiment for Children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coffee-ground-fossils-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Introducing children to the wonders of science and history can be both fun and educational. One creative way to do this is through a hands-on paleontology experiment using coffee ground fossils. This simple activity allows kids to learn about fossils, the process of fossilization, and ancient life&amp;mdash;all while having fun creating their own &amp;ldquo;fossils.&amp;rdquo;  In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll gu</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 15:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coffee-ground-fossils-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Barometer Experiment for Children: Guide to Understanding Air Pressure</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/barometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Teaching children about weather and atmospheric science becomes much more exciting when they can see real changes happening in front of them. A barometer is one of the most important tools used in weather forecasting, and creating a homemade version gives children a hands-on way to understand air pressure and how it affects the weather.  This simple barometer experiment uses everyday materials and</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 09:09:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/barometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Balloon &amp; Bottle Experiment: A Fun and Easy Air Pressure Activity for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-and-bottle-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>If you are looking for a simple, exciting, and highly visual science activity for kids, the balloon and bottle experiment is one of the best physics demonstrations to start with. This classic activity is not only fun but also helps children understand the concept of air pressure, vacuum, expansion, and the behavior of gases&amp;mdash;all using just a plastic bottle and a balloon.  What Is the Balloon </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 19:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-and-bottle-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Top Drupal LMS Features You Should Look For — Guide for your Education Businesses</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-lms-features-for-your-education-business.html</link>
			<description>If you run an education business today&amp;mdash;whether it&amp;rsquo;s an online academy, coaching platform, corporate training portal or skill-development institute&amp;mdash;choosing the right Learning Management System (LMS) is one of the most important decisions you will make. Your LMS becomes the backbone of your teaching, course delivery, student engagement and business growth.  Among the many LMS plat</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 17:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-lms-features-for-your-education-business.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to Fix the “.lima/colima/ha.sock: connect: connection refused” Error on macOS (Colima Issue Resolved)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-colima-connection-refused-error-failed-to-get-info-from-lima-colima-ha-sock-on-mac.html</link>
			<description>If you use Colima on macOS for container management, you may occasionally run into the error:  .lima/colima/ha.sock: connect: connection refused   This error appears simple, but for developers who rely on Colima for daily local development (especially with tools like DDEV), it can completely break your workflow. The good news? The issue has a clean, repeatable fix &amp;mdash; and this article explains</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2025 16:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-colima-connection-refused-error-failed-to-get-info-from-lima-colima-ha-sock-on-mac.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Leaf Breathing Experiment: Teach Kids About Photosynthesis</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-breathing-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Leaf Breathing - Investigating Transpiration Experiment  Objective: To explore the process of transpiration in plants by observing &amp;quot;leaf breathing&amp;quot; through the movement of water in a plant stem.  Materials:   Freshly cut leafy plant stem (e.g., a leafy branch from a tree or a herbaceous plant) Clear glass or container Water Food coloring (optional) Optional: Plastic wrap or transp</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 14:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-breathing-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rainforest in a Jar: Create a Mini Ecosystem With Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rainforest-in-a-jar-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a &amp;quot;Rainforest in a Jar&amp;quot; is a fun science project that helps kids learn about the water cycle and how rainforests work. This mini ecosystem shows how water evaporates, condenses and rains, just like in nature.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple guide to make your own rainforest in a jar:  Materials Needed:   Clear Glass Jar or Large Bowl: This will hold your mini rainforest. Plastic Wrap: To</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:56:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rainforest-in-a-jar-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Make Invisible Ink That Changes Color: Kids Science Activity</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-changing-invisible-ink-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Color-Changing Invisible Ink - Chemical Reaction Experiment  Objective: To create and reveal color-changing invisible ink using a simple chemical reaction.  Materials:   Lemon juice or white vinegar Water White paper or a blank sheet of paper Cotton swabs or small paintbrushes Heat source (hairdryer or iron) Optional: Food coloring for additional color effects   Procedure:   Create the invi</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:56:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-changing-invisible-ink-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Shadow Tracing Experiment: Learn Light &amp; Movement With Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/shadow-tracing-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Shadow tracing is an excellent way for children to explore concepts related to the Earth&amp;#39;s rotation, the position of the sun and how these factors affect shadow length and direction. This simple science experiment demonstrates how the position of the sun in the sky changes throughout the day and how this affects the shadows cast by objects. Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed guide on how to conduct this </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/shadow-tracing-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Build a Solar Still: Water Purification Science Project for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-still-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Solar still is a simple yet effective device for purifying water using solar energy. It works on the principle of evaporation and condensation to separate clean water from impurities.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to conducting a solar still experiment to demonstrate the process of water purification:  Materials Needed:   Clear Plastic Sheet: To cover the solar still and capture the evaporated </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-still-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to Set Up Solar Power at Home: Step-by-Step Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-setup-solar-power-for-you-home.html</link>
			<description>Setting up a solar power system for a family of four in India involves several steps. Please note that the costs provided are approximate and can vary based on factors like location, system size, quality of components and labor costs.  Additionally, government incentives and rebates can affect the final cost.  Step-by-Step Guide:  Step 1: Assess Your Energy Needs   Determine Your Energy Consumptio</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-setup-solar-power-for-you-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Secure Application Password Reset Flow: Best Practices</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-your-applications-reset-password-flow.html</link>
			<description>Generally any application framework provides users to have a flow to reset the passwords by default, It is more like, use clicking on the Reset Password link and redirects to a page where he will asked for email and reset link sent to users email, so that user can reset the password on their own.  This is a default or general flow that any application framework provides, but developers or architec</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-your-applications-reset-password-flow.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Mini Wind Turbine: Science Experiment for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mini-wind-turbine-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a mini wind turbine is a great science experiment for children that demonstrates the principles of wind energy and how it can be converted into electricity.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to creating a simple mini wind turbine using easily available materials:  Materials Needed:   Plastic Bottle: For the turbine&amp;#39;s body. Cardboard or Plastic Sheets: For the turbine blades. Wooden D</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mini-wind-turbine-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Implementing a Logger System Using the Singleton Pattern in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-logger-system-using-the-singleton-pattern-in-php.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we&amp;#39;ll create a simple logger system using the Singleton Pattern in PHP.  This logger will allow you to log messages to a file, ensuring that there is only one instance of the logger throughout your application.  Step-by-Step Implementation  Step 1: Create the Logger Class  We&amp;#39;ll start by defining a Logger class that follows the Singleton Pattern. This class will have metho</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-logger-system-using-the-singleton-pattern-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Build a Geodesic Dome: DIY Geometry Project for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-geodesic-dome-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a geodesic dome is an exciting and educational science experiment that helps children understand geometric principles, engineering concepts and structural design. A geodesic dome is a spherical structure composed of interconnected triangles, which provides a strong and stable framework.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide for creating a DIY geodesic dome using paper or straws.  Materials N</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-geodesic-dome-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Math Board Games: Educational Fun for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-math-board-games-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating and playing math-based board games is a fantastic way for children to learn math concepts while having fun. These DIY games can be tailored to various age groups and skill levels, making math practice engaging and interactive.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to designing and playing your own math board games.  Materials Needed:   Cardboard or Poster Board: For the game board. Markers o</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-math-board-games-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Pulley System: Science Experiment for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-it-yourself-pulley-system-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple DIY pulley system is a great way to introduce children to basic physics concepts like force and mechanical advantage.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can conduct a pulley system science experiment for children:  Materials:   Two sturdy hooks or fixed points (e.g., a door frame, tree branches, or any secure anchor points) String or rope Small bucket or container Objects with varying weights (</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-it-yourself-pulley-system-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to Charge Your Phone With Solar Power at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</link>
			<description>As the world shifts toward renewable energy, solar power is becoming an increasingly practical and eco-friendly way to charge everyday devices&amp;mdash;especially mobile phones. Whether you&amp;#39;re off the grid, on a camping trip, or simply looking to reduce your environmental impact, solar charging offers a convenient solution.  This article will walk you through how to charge your phone using solar </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to Cook Using Solar Power at Home: DIY Solar Cooking Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</link>
			<description>On PeoplesBLOG, we were writing articles related to Eco friendly homes and how to use Solar energy and along the same lines, in this article we are going to see how people can cook their food with Solar energy.  Generally majority of the people nowadays use Gas stoves for Cooking at home and Solar is one of the best case of the replacement for this. People can make a major change on the Environmen</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solar Panel Setup Guide: Installation, Usage &amp; Efficiency Tips</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Going green is the best of the environment and if you are planning to go green, then we all know Sun is the non-renewable energy and we could use this energy for people&amp;#39;s survival. We have a few articles at PeoplesBLOG related to the Environment and going green, have a check of them.  Using the Electricity from Solar energy is one of the best combinations, because there is not much waste out o</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Azure Front Door &amp; CDN Profiles: Concepts &amp; Best Practices</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-front-door-and-cdn-profiles-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</link>
			<description>In today&amp;rsquo;s cloud-first world, providing fast, reliable, and secure access to web applications is critical for a positive user experience. With users across different geographic regions, ensuring low-latency content delivery and application optimization is key to improving performance. Azure Front Door and Azure Content Delivery Network (CDN) are two essential services in Azure that help orga</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:37:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-front-door-and-cdn-profiles-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What Is a Solar Charge Controller? Guide for Home Solar Systems</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-charge-controller-and-how-to-use-it-with-a-solar-panel-setup-at-home.html</link>
			<description>A charge controller, also known as a charge regulator, is a crucial component in a solar panel system. Its primary function is to regulate the voltage and current coming from the solar panels and going to the battery bank.  Here&amp;#39;s how to use a charge controller in a home solar panel setup:  Purpose of a Charge Controller:   Prevents Overcharging: Charge controllers prevent overcharging of batt</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-charge-controller-and-how-to-use-it-with-a-solar-panel-setup-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Store Drupal Logs on AWS: A Practical Logging Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-drupal-logs-amazon-s.html</link>
			<description>Store Drupal logs on Amazon S3 via hook_watchdog, so that you can get rid of heavy logs on your drupal database and can later read from the S3.  For this todo on Drupal   You should use the &amp;quot;hook_watchdog&amp;quot; hook, where this hook allows modules to route log events to custom destinations. In our case, our custom destination will be S3. Initially we need to get the access to AWS and appropri</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:34:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-drupal-logs-amazon-s.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>SQL Transactions Explained: Atomic Operations &amp; Data Integrity</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sql-transactions-for-atomic-operations-ensuring-data-integrity-and-consistency.html</link>
			<description>Implementing transactions for atomic operations is crucial in ensuring data integrity and consistency, especially in databases and concurrent applications.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a high-level overview of how to implement transactions, focusing on the key concepts and techniques involved.  Key Concepts   Atomicity: Ensures that a series of operations either complete entirely or have no effect at all. If any</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sql-transactions-for-atomic-operations-ensuring-data-integrity-and-consistency.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Writing Secure SQL Queries: Use Prepared Statements in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/writing-secure-sql-queries-using-prepared-statements.html</link>
			<description>Writing secure SQL queries is crucial to prevent vulnerabilities such as SQL injection. Using prepared statements is one of the best practices to ensure that your SQL queries are safe.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a guide on how to do this effectively.  What are Prepared Statements?  Prepared statements are a feature of many database management systems (DBMS) that allow you to define a SQL query template and the</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/writing-secure-sql-queries-using-prepared-statements.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solar Oven Experiment: Cook With Sunlight – A Kid’s Science Project</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-oven-cooking-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building and using a DIY solar oven is a fantastic way to explore solar energy and understand the principles of cooking with sunlight. A solar oven harnesses solar energy to heat and cook food, providing a practical demonstration of renewable energy in action.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to creating and using a simple solar oven:  Materials Needed:   Cardboard Box: A large, clean cardboard </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-oven-cooking-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Data Structures in PHP: Stacks, Queues, Linked Lists &amp; SPL</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/data-structures-in-php-implementing-stacks-queues-linked-lists-and-spl-classes.html</link>
			<description>Data structures are an integral part of programming, offering efficient ways to store and organize data. As PHP evolves, understanding how to implement and utilize common data structures like Stacks, Queues, and Linked Lists will make you a more proficient PHP developer. PHP 8 provides a range of options, from manual implementations to built-in SPL (Standard PHP Library) classes that offer high pe</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:26:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/data-structures-in-php-implementing-stacks-queues-linked-lists-and-spl-classes.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Balloon Rocket Experiment: Launch Science for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-rocket-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The balloon rocket experiment is a simple and exciting way to explore the principles of action and reaction, or Newton&amp;#39;s Third Law of Motion.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can conduct the balloon rocket science experiment for children:  Materials:   Balloon String or thread (about 10-15 feet) Drinking straw Tape Scissors   Procedure:   Prepare the &amp;quot;Rocket&amp;quot; Assembly:   Cut a piece of string or </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-rocket-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Water Fountain: Fun Science Experiment Using Air Pressure</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-water-fountain-using-air-pressure-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a water fountain using air pressure can be an engaging and educational project.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple way to make a small-scale water fountain using air pressure:  Materials Needed:   Plastic bottle Drinking straw Hot glue gun and glue sticks Scissors Tape Water Optional: Food coloring (for colored water)   Instructions:   Prepare the Bottle:   Take a plastic bottle and remove the cap. Use</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:24:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-water-fountain-using-air-pressure-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>SOLID Principles in PHP: A Developer’s Guide to Clean Code</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-solid-principles-in-php.html</link>
			<description>The SOLID principles are a set of five fundamental design principles in object-oriented programming aimed at improving software design, making it more understandable, flexible and maintainable. These principles are especially relevant for developers working with PHP and similar languages.  Let&amp;#39;s dive into each principle, exploring its meaning and how it can be applied effectively in PHP.  1. S</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:23:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-solid-principles-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best Batteries for Home Solar Panels: Types &amp; Buying Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-batteries-to-use-with-the-solar-panels-for-home.html</link>
			<description>When it comes to choosing batteries for a solar panel system, several options are available. The best battery for your home will depend on factors like budget, energy requirements, available space and desired lifespan.  Here are some of the most common types:   Lithium-Ion Batteries:   Advantages:   High energy density, which means they can store a lot of energy in a relatively small space. Long l</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:23:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-batteries-to-use-with-the-solar-panels-for-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Potato Battery: Build a Homemade Power Source with Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-potato-battery-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a DIY potato battery is a fascinating and educational experiment that demonstrates the basics of electrochemical cells and how chemical energy can be converted into electrical energy.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to building a potato battery using zinc and copper electrodes:  Materials Needed:   Potatoes: 2-3 medium-sized potatoes (or more if you want to create a battery with higher v</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-potato-battery-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Volcano Experiment: Baking Soda &amp; Vinegar Fun for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-volcanic-eruption-with-baking-soda-and-vinegar.html</link>
			<description>Creating a volcanic eruption with baking soda and vinegar is a classic and safe science experiment that demonstrates the reaction between an acid (vinegar) and a base (baking soda) to produce carbon dioxide gas.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Baking soda Vinegar Dish soap (optional) Red food coloring (optional) Container or plastic bottle Modeling clay or playdough Tray or </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-volcanic-eruption-with-baking-soda-and-vinegar.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Build an Anemometer: Wind Speed Science Experiment for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/anemometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a simple anemometer is a fun and educational science experiment that allows children to measure the wind speed and understand how wind speed is quantified. By defination, an anemometer is a device that measures wind velocity by counting number of times its blades spin in a given time period.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step process for creating a basic anemometer using everyday materials:  Mate</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/anemometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Database Design Basics: Normalization, Relationships &amp; ER Diagrams</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/basics-of-database-design-normalization-relationships-and-er-diagrams.html</link>
			<description>Database design is a critical phase in creating a robust, scalable and efficient database system. It involves structuring data in a way that ensures it can be stored, retrieved and managed effectively. Some key concepts fundamental to database design are Normalization, Relationships and Entity-Relationship (ER) Diagrams.  Let&amp;#39;s explore these concepts in detail.  1. Normalization  Normalization</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/basics-of-database-design-normalization-relationships-and-er-diagrams.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Build a Wind Vane: Easy Science Project for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/wind-vane-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple wind vane is a fun and educational science experiment for children that helps them understand wind direction and meteorological concepts. A wind vane, or weather vane, indicates the direction from which the wind is blowing.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to building a basic wind vane using common materials:  Materials Needed:   Plastic Straw or Wooden Dowel: For the central a</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/wind-vane-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Milk Bottle Xylophone: Colorful &amp; Fun Music Experiment for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/milk-bottle-xylophone-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Milk Bottle Xylophone - Sound and Pitch Experiment  Objective: To explore sound and pitch by creating a milk bottle xylophone.  Materials:   Empty glass milk bottles (varying sizes) Water Wooden sticks or metal spoons (for striking the bottles) Optional: Food coloring or colored tape (for visual effect)   Procedure:   Gather a set of empty glass milk bottles. You can use bottles of differen</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/milk-bottle-xylophone-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Leaf Chromatography: Easy Science Experiment for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-chromatography-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Leaf chromatography is a simple and fascinating experiment that introduces children to the concept of chromatography, which separates different pigments in leaves.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Fresh green leaves (different types if possible) Coffee filters or chromatography paper Pencil Small glasses or jars Rubbing alcohol or isopropyl alcohol Water Tape Small weights or paperc</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-chromatography-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Floating Fish Experiment: Fun Science Activity for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/floating-fish-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Floating Fish - Density and Buoyancy Experiment  Objective: To explore the concepts of density and buoyancy by creating a floating fish.  Materials:   Clay or playdough Plasticine or modeling clay Plastic toy fish or small plastic object A basin, tub, or container filled with water   Procedure:   Start by shaping the plasticine or modeling clay into a small ball or disc shape. This will ser</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:09:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/floating-fish-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Azure Key Vault: Key Concepts &amp; Security Best Practices</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-key-vault-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</link>
			<description>In the modern cloud-driven world, security is more critical than ever. Organizations are increasingly migrating their data, applications, and infrastructure to the cloud, but with this transition comes the need to protect sensitive information such as secrets, keys, certificates, and passwords. Azure Key Vault is a cloud service provided by Microsoft Azure designed specifically to safeguard and ma</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:03:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-key-vault-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Azure Active Directory &amp; App Registrations: Complete Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-active-directory-azure-app-registrations-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</link>
			<description>In the modern world of cloud computing, managing identity and access is crucial to securing enterprise applications and data. Microsoft Azure provides a comprehensive identity and access management solution through Azure Active Directory (Azure AD). Whether you are managing an enterprise IT environment or building cloud-based applications, understanding Azure AD and Azure App Registrations is foun</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:03:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-active-directory-azure-app-registrations-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Azure Storage Accounts: Concepts, Setup &amp; Best Practices</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-storage-accounts-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</link>
			<description>Azure Storage is a cloud service provided by Microsoft Azure that allows users to store and manage data in a highly scalable, secure, and cost-effective manner. One of the core components of Azure Storage is the Azure Storage Account. An Azure Storage Account provides a unique namespace for storing data in Azure and serves as the container for different types of storage services, such as Blob Stor</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:03:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-storage-accounts-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS): Key Concepts &amp; Best Practices</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-kubernetes-service-aks-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</link>
			<description>As the adoption of cloud-native technologies grows, Kubernetes has become the de facto standard for orchestrating containerized applications. Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) is Microsoft&amp;#39;s managed Kubernetes offering in the Azure cloud, designed to simplify the deployment, management, and scaling of containerized applications. AKS helps organizations take advantage of Kubernetes&amp;#39; robust fea</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-kubernetes-service-aks-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Implement One-to-Many &amp; Many-to-Many Relationships in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-one-to-many-and-many-to-many-relationships.html</link>
			<description>Implementing one-to-many and many-to-many relationships in a database is essential for accurately modeling real-world scenarios.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed look at how to set up these relationships in a relational database.  One-to-Many Relationship  A one-to-many relationship occurs when a single record in one table can relate to multiple records in another table.  Example Scenario: Consider a User</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-one-to-many-and-many-to-many-relationships.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cloud in a Bottle: Fun Science Experiment for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cloud-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a cloud in a bottle is a fantastic and visually engaging science experiment that demonstrates the basic principles of cloud formation. This simple experiment uses everyday materials to mimic the process of cloud formation in a controlled environment.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to performing the &amp;ldquo;Cloud in a Bottle&amp;rdquo; experiment:  Materials Needed:   Plastic Bottle: A clea</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cloud-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Setup Multisite Local Environment with DDEV &amp; Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-ddev-and-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how we can set up a multisite environment with ddev on the local machine. Assuming people are aware of configuring the drupal multiple site from the drupal side of configurations.  As we all know ddev is an open source tool for running local PHP development environments in minutes, which makes developer life easier during the local environment setup process, her</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-ddev-and-drupal.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>