<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Travel - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/travel.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Bangalore to Srikalahasti Solo Trip Guide – Route, Temple Timings &amp; Itinerary</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srikalahasti-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Srikalahasti is a rewarding journey, especially for those seeking a peaceful break with spiritual significance. Srikalahasti, famous for its ancient Shiva temple and the unique Vayu Linga, attracts devotees and travelers throughout the year. This guide expands on the original plan and gives a more useful, updated structure for anyone planning the same route.  Route Ov</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srikalahasti-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Srisailam Solo Trip Plan: Route, Temples &amp; Tips</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srisailam-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A trip from Bangalore to Srisailam is one of the best short pilgrimages you can plan for 2 to 3 days. Whether you are riding solo on a motorbike or travelling with your family in a car, this travel plan will help you cover Srisailam, Alampur, and another Shakti Peetha smoothly.  Srisailam is a unique place where you can visit Lord Mallikarjuna (one of the 12 Jyotirlingas) and Goddess Bhramaramba (</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srisailam-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Rameswaram Trip Plan: 3-Day Itinerary &amp; Tips</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-rameswaram--days--nights-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A road trip from Bangalore to Rameswaram is one of the most memorable long-drive experiences in South India. Whether you&amp;#39;re a couple travelling on a bike or a family driving in a car, this 3-day travel plan covers everything you need &amp;mdash; routes, timings, important stops, temple order, Dhanushkodi plan and safety tips.  This upgraded travel guide helps you plan your trip without confusion, </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-rameswaram--days--nights-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Horanadu Solo Trip Plan: Complete Travel Itinerary</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-horanadu-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Horanadu is one of the most peaceful and rewarding getaways you can experience in Karnataka. Whether you are riding alone on a motorcycle or travelling with family in a car, this route gives you a perfect mix of spirituality, Western Ghats beauty, and calm mountain roads. The main highlight of this journey is visiting the famous Horanadu Sri Annapoorneshwari Temple, o</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-horanadu-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Dharmasthala Solo Trip Plan: Route &amp; Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One or Two days Trip from Bangalore to Dharmasthala to Bangalore, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this one or two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Dharmasthala is a small Hindu </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Bheemeshwari: Solo Nature Trip &amp; Fishing Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-bheemeshwari-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Bheemeshwari can be a peaceful and adventurous experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the serene nature, engage in activities like fishing and river rafting and enjoy the tranquility of this riverside destination in Karnataka. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Ramanagara -&amp;gt; Channapatna -&amp;gt; Halagur -&amp;gt; Channapatna -&amp;gt; Rama</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-bheemeshwari-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Mekedatu Gorge: Solo Adventure Trip Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mekedatu-gorge-adventure-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Mekedatu, meaning &amp;ldquo;Goat&amp;rsquo;s Leap&amp;rdquo; in Kannada, is a breathtaking gorge where the Cauvery River flows through narrow rock formations. Located about 100 km from Bangalore, it is an excellent destination for a solo adventure, offering stunning landscapes, river views, and an exciting trek. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for an escape into nature, this guide will help you plan a seamless journ</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mekedatu-gorge-adventure-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to Charge Your Phone With Solar Power at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</link>
			<description>As the world shifts toward renewable energy, solar power is becoming an increasingly practical and eco-friendly way to charge everyday devices&amp;mdash;especially mobile phones. Whether you&amp;#39;re off the grid, on a camping trip, or simply looking to reduce your environmental impact, solar charging offers a convenient solution.  This article will walk you through how to charge your phone using solar </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, Bangalore to Kathmandu then to Salleri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to trek Solo to Everest Base Camp by yourself from Bangalore, then this article will help you to get a picture of how to reach Salleri from Bangalore, where Salleri will be the starting point of Trek to Everest Base Camp.  There are many possible routes to reach Kathmandu from Bangalore.   Flight  There are direct flights from Bangalore to Kathmandu and vice versa. You also hav</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:38:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Jaipur to Tonk: Exploring the City of Havelis &amp; Heritage</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jaipur-to-tonk-exploring-the-city-of-havelis.html</link>
			<description>If you&amp;#39;re in Jaipur and looking for a short, historical getaway, Tonk, known as the &amp;quot;City of Havelis,&amp;quot; is an ideal destination. This quaint town, just 96 kilometers from Jaipur, is rich in cultural heritage and showcases the grandeur of Rajasthani architecture. Whether you&amp;#39;re a history enthusiast, an architecture lover, or someone looking for a peaceful retreat, Tonk has somethin</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jaipur-to-tonk-exploring-the-city-of-havelis.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>4-Day Solo Trip to Gokarna: Beaches, Temples &amp; Itinerary</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</link>
			<description>You are planning to visit Gokarna solo then here is the article which will help you to plan your trip. And this plan in this article is for three days and four nights and for a person who wants to travel solo.  If you are traveling from Bangalore, overnight bus or a train will be the best option for travel to Gokarna. And if you wish to travel via flight, the nearest airport for people will be eit</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Hampi: Solo Trip Plan + Historic Route Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-hampi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Hampi is perfect for anyone who wants a break from city life and enjoys history, architecture and wide, open landscapes. Hampi was once the capital of the Vijayanagara Empire, one of the richest kingdoms of its time, and today the region stands as a UNESCO World Heritage Site filled with ancient ruins, boulders and river-side villages. This guide combines practical tr</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-hampi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Hyderabad: Solo Trip Itinerary &amp; Travel Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-hyderabad-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Planning a trip from Bangalore to Hyderabad can be an exciting adventure! One day trip or Two day trip from Bangalore to Hyderabad, If you are&amp;nbsp;Solo&amp;nbsp;riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover places in Hyderabad.  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Anantapur -&amp;gt; Kurnool -&amp;gt; Hyderabad -&amp;gt; Bangalore  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:34:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-hyderabad-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>10 Best Solo Travel Destinations in South India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-places-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo in South India can be a remarkable experience, offering a diverse range of landscapes, cultures and experiences.  Here are ten of the best places to explore, along with reasons why they are great for solo travelers and the best times to visit:   Pondicherry, Tamil Nadu:   Why: Pondicherry offers a unique blend of French and Indian cultures, serene beaches and a peaceful ambiance. It</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-places-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Murdeshwar, Gokarna, Goa and Dandeli Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-murdeshwar-gokarna-goa-dandeli.html</link>
			<description>Ten days Ride from Bangalore Murdeshwar Gokarna Goa Dandeli Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are riding with a Friend in two different Bikes, then this plan for ten days works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Route  Bang</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-murdeshwar-gokarna-goa-dandeli.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Lepakshi: Solo Trip Plan &amp; Temple Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One day trip from Bangalore to Lepakshi, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this one day plan works very well.  Lepakshi is a small village located in Anantapur district, Andhra Pradesh. It is around 120 KM from Bangalore. It is famous for Veerabhadra temple, one of the oldest temples in India. The temple has Ganesha, Nandi, Veerabhadra, Shiva, Bhadrak</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:32:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Coorg: Solo Itinerary &amp; Tips for a Peaceful Getaway</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-coorg-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Coorg can be a wonderful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the lush green landscapes, coffee plantations and serene natural beauty of this hill station in Karnataka. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your journey:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Mysore -&amp;gt; Coorg -&amp;gt; Madikeri -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Mysore -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Coorg   Start your trip early </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:31:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-coorg-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Night Riding Tips for Motorcyclists: Stay Safe on Highways</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-for-night-driving-on-motorcycle-on-roads-and-highways.html</link>
			<description>Driving during night will have few advantages and yes it comes with being very careful and prepared as well. And sharing this article particularly for the Motorcycle riders.  Night driving will have few advantages for people, like no need to worry about the huge traffic because most of the people will be sleeping, And you will not get tired like you get tired in the daytime, And most of the night </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-for-night-driving-on-motorcycle-on-roads-and-highways.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Chennai to Vedanthangal: Solo Bird Sanctuary Trip Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/chennai-to-vedanthangal-bird-sanctuary-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Vedanthangal Bird Sanctuary, located in Tamil Nadu, is one of the oldest bird sanctuaries in India. Just 80 kilometers from Chennai, it is a paradise for bird watchers and nature enthusiasts. This sanctuary is home to a variety of migratory birds and provides a tranquil escape from the city&amp;rsquo;s hustle and bustle.  If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a solo trip, here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed guide to help you </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:26:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/chennai-to-vedanthangal-bird-sanctuary-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Trivandrum: Solo Trip Itinerary &amp; Travel Tips</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-trivandrum-solo-travel-plan.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo from Bangalore to Trivandrum is a refreshing experience, especially if you enjoy culture, beaches, history and relaxed city life. Trivandrum (Thiruvananthapuram), the capital of Kerala, blends tradition with natural beauty, making it a perfect destination for a peaceful solo getaway.  Here is a detailed and easy-to-follow plan for your trip.  How to Travel From Bangalore to Trivandr</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:26:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-trivandrum-solo-travel-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Jog Falls: Solo Travel Itinerary &amp; Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-jog-falls-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Jog Falls can be a refreshing experience, especially for nature lovers. Jog Falls, located in the Shimoga district of Karnataka, is one of the highest plunge waterfalls in India.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Jog Falls   Begin your journey early in the morning to make the most of the day. The distance between Bangalore and Jog Falls</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:24:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-jog-falls-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Udupi Solo Trip Plan: Temple, Beaches &amp; Tips</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-udupi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Udupi can be a delightful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the pristine beaches, ancient temples and delicious cuisine of this coastal town in Karnataka.  Udupi is one of the top tourist attractions in Karnataka and has various educational institutions. It is notable for the&amp;nbsp;Krishna Temple&amp;nbsp;and is also known as the temple city.[3]&amp;nbsp;It also lends its</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:23:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-udupi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Dandeli: Solo Trip Plan + Adventure Itinerary</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dandeli-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Dandeli promises an exciting adventure amidst nature, wildlife and thrilling activities.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Day 1: Bangalore to Dandeli   Morning: Departure from Bangalore   Start your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between Bangalore and Dandeli is approximately 460 kilometers and the drive tak</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dandeli-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kanakapura: Perfect Day Trip Guide with Kayaking</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanakapura-kayaking-spot-a-perfect-day-trip-guide.html</link>
			<description>If you&amp;#39;re looking for an adventurous escape from Bangalore, Kanakapura is an ideal destination. Located just 55 kilometers from the city, this serene spot offers exciting kayaking experiences amid lush greenery and scenic landscapes.  In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll go over everything you need to know about making the most out of a day trip from Bangalore to Kanakapura, including the route, itine</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanakapura-kayaking-spot-a-perfect-day-trip-guide.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Talakadu: Couple’s Motorcycle Ride &amp; Travel Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-talakadu-historical-site-a-couple-motorcycle-ride-travel-plan.html</link>
			<description>Talakadu, on the banks of the river Kaveri, is a fascinating blend of history, mythology, and natural beauty. Once a flourishing city with more than 30 temples, Talakadu is today partly buried under shifting sand dunes, earning it the name &amp;ldquo;The Desert of Karnataka.&amp;rdquo; For a couple riding out of Bangalore on a motorcycle, this trip is the perfect mix of adventure, romance, and heritage. T</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-talakadu-historical-site-a-couple-motorcycle-ride-travel-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Tiruvannamalai Solo Trip: Complete Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruvannamalai-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Tiruvannamalai, a sacred town in Tamil Nadu, is renowned for the Arunachaleswarar Temple and the spiritual aura that surrounds the holy Arunachala hill. Just 200 km from Bangalore, it makes for a serene solo getaway&amp;mdash;whether you&amp;rsquo;re seeking divine connection, introspection, or a peaceful retreat in nature. Here&amp;rsquo;s your complete solo travel guide from Bangalore to Tiruvannamalai.  Ro</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruvannamalai-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kanipakam Solo Trip: Temple &amp; Travel Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanipakam-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Kanipakam, located in Chittoor district of Andhra Pradesh, is a renowned pilgrimage destination famous for the Sri Varasiddhi Vinayaka Temple. Known for its divine atmosphere and spiritual significance, the temple attracts devotees from across South India. A solo trip from Bangalore to Kanipakam is perfect for those seeking peace, devotion, and personal reflection.  Route from Bangalore to Kanipak</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanipakam-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Thekkady Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-thekkady-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Thekkady is one of the best ways to unwind, explore nature and enjoy a peaceful break. Thekkady, located in Kerala&amp;rsquo;s Idukki district, is famous for the Periyar Wildlife Sanctuary, spice plantations, lush green hills and calm backwaters. Whether you love wildlife, photography, food, or long road trips, this journey offers something for everyone.  This guide gives</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-thekkady-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Alleppey Solo Trip: Backwaters &amp; Travel Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-alleppey-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Alleppey (Alappuzha) can be a memorable experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the backwaters, houseboat cruises and serene beauty of the famous backwater destination in Kerala. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Coimbatore -&amp;gt; Kochi -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Alleppey  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Maddur -&amp;gt; Chamarajanagar -&amp;gt; Coimbatore -&amp;g</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-alleppey-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kanyakumari Solo Trip: Travel Guide &amp; Itinerary</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanyakumari-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Kanyakumari can be a fascinating journey, as you&amp;#39;ll get to experience the diverse landscapes, cultural heritage and the meeting point of the Arabian Sea, the Indian Ocean and the Bay of Bengal. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Madurai -&amp;gt; Kanyakumari -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Salem -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Madur</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanyakumari-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kovalam Solo Trip: Complete Travel Itinerary</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kovalam-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Kovalam offers a perfect blend of relaxation, beach vibes and cultural experiences.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Madurai -&amp;gt; Tirunelveli -&amp;gt; Nagercoil -&amp;gt; Kovalam  Bangalore to Kovalam   Departure from Bangalore   Start your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kovalam-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Tiruttani Solo Trip: Complete Travel Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruttani-solo-travel-plan.html</link>
			<description>Tiruttani is one of the most important pilgrimage destinations in Tamil Nadu and a sacred place deeply connected to the worship of Lord Murugan. The Tiruttani Murugan Temple stands on a hilltop blessed with centuries of faith, devotion and ancient history. For a solo traveler, the town offers a combination of calmness, spirituality, light trekking, cultural experiences and an escape from the rush </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruttani-solo-travel-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Varkala Solo Trip: Beach &amp; Travel Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-varkala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Varkala is a perfect way to unwind and recharge. Varkala, a picturesque coastal town in Kerala, is famous for its cliffs overlooking the Arabian Sea, pristine beaches, backwaters, and spiritual significance. This journey combines scenic drives through the Western Ghats, serene beach experiences, cultural insights, and relaxation.  Whether you are a solo traveler seeki</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-varkala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ahmedabad to Shamlaji Temple: Complete Pilgrimage Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ahmedabad-to-shamlaji-temple-pilgrimage.html</link>
			<description>The Shamlaji Temple, also known as the Shamlaji Vishnu Mandir, is one of Gujarat&amp;#39;s most revered pilgrimage sites. Nestled amidst the picturesque Aravalli Hills, the temple is dedicated to Lord Vishnu and attracts thousands of devotees each year. Located about 120 kilometers from Ahmedabad, Shamlaji Temple is a perfect destination for a peaceful spiritual retreat.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed artic</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:51:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ahmedabad-to-shamlaji-temple-pilgrimage.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Sakleshpur Solo Trip: Complete Travel Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-sakleshpur-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Sakleshpur offers an ideal getaway amidst the serene Western Ghats, lush greenery and pleasant weather.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Sakleshpur   Departure from Bangalore   Start your journey early in the morning to avoid traffic and make the most of your day. The distance between Bangalore and Sakleshpur is approximately 220 kilom</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-sakleshpur-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Madurai Solo Trip: Travel Itinerary &amp; Tips</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-madurai-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Madurai can be a fascinating journey, rich in history, culture and spirituality. Madurai, often referred to as the Athens of the East, is famous for its Meenakshi Amman Temple and vibrant street life.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Madurai   Begin your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between Ba</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-madurai-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kollur Solo Trip Plan: Complete Travel Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kollur-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Kollur can be a serene and spiritually enriching experience, as Kollur is home to the famous Mookambika Temple.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Kollur   Start your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between Bangalore and Kollur is approximately 400 kilometers and the drive takes around 8-9 hours. R</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:47:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kollur-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Anamudi Solo Trip: Complete Itinerary &amp; Tips</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-anamudi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Anamudi, standing as the highest peak in the Western Ghats and South India, is a wonderful destination for nature lovers and trekkers. It&amp;#39;s situated in the Eravikulam National Park near Munnar, Kerala.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip from Bangalore to Anamudi:  Bangalore to Munnar   Begin your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-anamudi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kudremukh Solo Trip: Travel Guide &amp; Tips</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kudremukh-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Kudremukh is one of the best short getaways you can take if you enjoy mountains, quiet landscapes, and nature. Kudremukh is famous for its rolling green valleys, deep forests and the iconic peak that resembles a horse&amp;rsquo;s face&amp;mdash;giving the mountain its name Kuduremukha in Kannada. Historically, it was also known as Samseparvata since it was accessed from Samse</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kudremukh-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Chitradurga Solo Trip Plan: Complete Itinerary</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chitradurga-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Chitradurga is one of the most accessible and rewarding short journeys you can plan in Karnataka. Known for its historic fort, rocky landscape, windmill fields and calm environment, Chitradurga serves as an excellent weekend destination for travellers who want a mix of history, nature and peaceful exploration.  This guide expands on your original content while keeping</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chitradurga-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Ghati Short Trip Guide: One-Day Itinerary</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/short-trip-from-bangalore-to-ghati.html</link>
			<description>A one-day trip from Bangalore to Ghati Subramanya is perfect whether you are riding solo on a motorbike or driving with family in a car. Ghati Subramanya is an ancient Hindu temple, located about 50 kilometers from Bangalore towards Doddaballapur, making it ideal for a short morning getaway. The temple is surrounded by scenic village roads and offers a peaceful spiritual experience combined with a</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/short-trip-from-bangalore-to-ghati.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Agumbe Solo Trip: Travel Itinerary &amp; Tips</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-agumbe-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Agumbe can be a thrilling adventure, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the rainforests, waterfalls and scenic beauty of the Western Ghats in Karnataka. Agumbe is also known as the &amp;quot;Cherrapunji of South India&amp;quot; due to its high rainfall and lush greenery.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Hassan -&amp;gt; Belur -&amp;gt; Sringeri -&amp;gt; A</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:38:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-agumbe-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kukke Subramanya Trip Plan: Complete Travel Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kukke-subramanya-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Planning a trip from Bangalore to Kukke Subramanya is always a refreshing idea, whether you are a solo rider on a motorbike or a family driving in a car. The journey offers a mix of spirituality, scenic ghats, calm forests and peaceful rural landscapes. One, two or even three days can be perfectly spent exploring this region, depending on how much you want to cover.  Kukke Subramanya is one of the</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 09:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kukke-subramanya-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Manali Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-manali-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A one-week trip from Bangalore to Manali works well for solo riders, families, and couples. This plan follows a simple route and covers all major places at a relaxed pace. Travellers may add or skip places depending on interest and time.  Manali is a popular hill station known for snow ranges, rivers, old temples, cafés, adventure sports, and peaceful weather.  Route Overview  Bangalore → Delhi</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 15:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-manali-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Savandurga Rock Trek – Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-savandurga-rock-trek-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Savandurga, known as one of the largest monolith hills in Asia, is a popular trekking destination located just 60 km from Bangalore. With its rugged trails, panoramic views, and historical ruins, it offers an ideal solo trekking experience for adventure lovers and nature enthusiasts alike. Whether you're seeking a quick escape or a physical challenge, this guide will help you plan your solo advent</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-savandurga-rock-trek-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Time Travel Possibilities in Quantum Physics</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/time-travel-possibilities-in-quantum-physics.html</link>
			<description>Time travel has long been a fascination in science fiction, but could it actually be possible? While classical physics suggests that time flows in a straight line from past to future, quantum physics introduces concepts that challenge our understanding of time. Some physicists believe that time travel might not only be possible but may already be happening at a microscopic level. In this article, </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 12:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/time-travel-possibilities-in-quantum-physics.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are some good tips and tricks to travel cheap?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-some-good-tips-and-tricks-to-travel-cheap.html</link>
			<description>Traveling on a budget can be both rewarding and challenging.  Here are some tips and tricks to help you travel cheaply while still having an enriching and enjoyable experience:  Planning and Preparation   Flexible Travel Dates:   Being flexible with your travel dates can help you find cheaper flights and accommodations. Use tools like Google Flights or Skyscanner to compare prices over a range of </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 20:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-some-good-tips-and-tricks-to-travel-cheap.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How can I meet new people when traveling alone?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-i-meet-new-people-when-traveling-alone.html</link>
			<description>Meeting new people while traveling alone can make your trip more exciting and create wonderful memories.  Here are some great ways to connect with others during your solo travels:  1. Stay in Social Places   Hostels:   Hostels are perfect for solo travelers. They often have shared spaces like lounges or kitchens where guests can hang out. Join in on hostel activities, group outings, or simply chat</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 09:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-i-meet-new-people-when-traveling-alone.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are the positives of traveling alone?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-positives-of-traveling-alone.html</link>
			<description>Traveling alone can be a transformative and enriching experience, offering a range of positives that contribute to personal growth, self-discovery and independence.  Here are some of the key benefits of traveling alone:  1. Self-Discovery and Personal Growth   Freedom to Explore: Traveling alone allows you to set your own pace, make your own decisions and explore places that genuinely interest you</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 08:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-positives-of-traveling-alone.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are some inexpensive methods of traveling?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-some-inexpensive-methods-of-traveling.html</link>
			<description>Traveling on a budget can be a fulfilling and exciting experience.  Here are some inexpensive methods and tips to help you travel affordably:  1. Transportation  Flights   Flight Comparison Websites: Use sites like Skyscanner, Kayak and Google Flights to compare prices and find the best deals. Budget Airlines: Consider flying with budget carriers like Ryanair, EasyJet and Southwest Airlines. Fle</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 06:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-some-inexpensive-methods-of-traveling.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>