<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Varkala - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/varkala.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>10 Best Beaches in India for Solo Travelers (Safe, Peaceful &amp; Budget-Friendly Guide)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-beaches-to-travel-solo-in-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo is one of the most rewarding experiences in life. It gives you freedom, confidence, space for self-discovery, and the chance to explore at your own pace. India, with its long coastline and diverse coastal landscapes, offers some of the most beautiful and safe beaches for solo travelers.  Whether you want peace, adventure, nightlife, yoga retreats, or breathtaking scenery, India has </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:24:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-beaches-to-travel-solo-in-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Varkala Solo Trip: Beach &amp; Travel Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-varkala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Varkala is a perfect way to unwind and recharge. Varkala, a picturesque coastal town in Kerala, is famous for its cliffs overlooking the Arabian Sea, pristine beaches, backwaters, and spiritual significance. This journey combines scenic drives through the Western Ghats, serene beach experiences, cultural insights, and relaxation.  Whether you are a solo traveler seeki</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Nov 2025 08:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-varkala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Trivandrum: Solo Trip Itinerary &amp; Travel Tips</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-trivandrum-solo-travel-plan.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo from Bangalore to Trivandrum is a refreshing experience, especially if you enjoy culture, beaches, history and relaxed city life. Trivandrum (Thiruvananthapuram), the capital of Kerala, blends tradition with natural beauty, making it a perfect destination for a peaceful solo getaway.  Here is a detailed and easy-to-follow plan for your trip.  How to Travel From Bangalore to Trivandr</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 10:26:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-trivandrum-solo-travel-plan.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>